Guide to the Syria Collection of photographs AD.MC.036
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Actor Headshots Series (Box 5)
  - A group portrait of a veiled woman and two men., Circa 1965-1975; ref683; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.8 x 17.9 cm (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Men; Women; Canes/Walking Sticks; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Costumes; Facial Hair; Actors
- Party Series (Box 5)
  - a group portrait of four women eating and smoking (linked ref816)., Circa 1940-1965; ref815; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Women; Food; Jewelry; Smoking; Parties; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of three women (linked ref815)., Circa 1940-1965; ref816; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7 cm (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Men; Women; Parties; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of several people around a set table., Circa 1940-1965; ref817; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.6 cm (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Men; Women; Regional/National Dress; Drinks/Beverages; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Parties; Syria
  - A group portrait of a man and a woman (linked ref819)., Circa 1940-1965; ref818; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.6 x 7.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Men; Women; Drinks/Beverages; Parties; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of a man and a woman (linked ref818)., Circa 1940-1965; ref819; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.2 x 6.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Men; Women; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Parties; Syria
  - A group portrait of several women sitting on a couch (linked ref821)., Circa 1940-1965; ref820; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.6 cm (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Women; Group Portraits; Syria; Parties; Photographic Prints
  - A group portrait of several women sitting on a couch (linked ref820)., Circa 1940-1965; ref821; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 6.9 cm (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Women; Syria; Parties; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of several men and a woman around a table., Circa 1940-1965; ref822; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.6 x 7.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Men; Smoking; Regional/National Dress; Women; Photographic Prints; Syria; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Parties
  - A group portrait of two men and one woman., Circa 1940-1965; ref823; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Men; Facial Hair; Women; Parties; Syria; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of two men and a girl., Circa 1940-1965; ref824; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.6 x 7.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Men; Girls; Children; Parties; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of several people around a table., Circa 1940-1965; ref825; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.6 x 7.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - A group portrait of five people sitting on a couch., Circa 1940-1965; ref826; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 6.2 cm (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Men; Women; Girls; Children; Syria; Parties; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of several women and children inside., Circa 1940-1965; ref827; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7 cm (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Girls; Children; Men; Photographic Prints; Parties; Women; Syria; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of a man and a woman (linked ref819)., Circa 1940-1965; ref828; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7 cm (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - A group portrait of two women and a man (linked ref828)., Circa 1940-1965; ref829; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.1 x 6.7 cm (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Men; Women; Parties; Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits
- Aleppo Series (Box 6)
  - An aerial landscape of a village., Circa 1930-1950; ref890; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Aleppo, Syria; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Airplanes
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref891; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.8 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Aleppo, Syria; Airplanes; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings
  - An aerial landscape of a village., Circa 1930-1950; ref892; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 x 8.4 cm (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Airplanes; Aleppo, Syria; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of several men and a woman looking out over a city., Circa 1930-1950; ref893; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 12.4 x 8.4 cm (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Men; Women; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Uniforms
  - An aerial landscape of a village., Circa 1930-1950; ref894; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.2 x 8.2 cm (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Airplanes; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - A group portrait of several men looking at the ground, taken from a rocky interior., Circa 1930-1950; ref895; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.2 x 8 cm (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Caves; Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - An aerial photo of the Citadel of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref896; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Aleppo, Syria; Airplanes; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Citadel of Aleppo
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref897; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.7 x 8 cm (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Buildings; Aleppo, Syria; Airplanes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Photographic Prints
  - A portrait of a man on horseback., Circa 1930-1950; ref898; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.6 x 8 cm (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Animals; Horses; Men; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref899; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Buildings; Aleppo, Syria; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Airplanes
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref900; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11 x 8 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Buildings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Aleppo, Syria; Airplanes
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref901; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.3 x 8.3 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Buildings; Airplanes
  - An aerial landscape of a village., Circa 1930-1950; ref902; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.1 x 8 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Airplanes; Buildings; Aleppo, Syria
  - A landscape of mountains with a tree in the foreground., Circa 1930-1950; ref903; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11 x 8.4 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Mountains/Hills; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - An aerial landscape of a village., Circa 1930-1950; ref904; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 x 8 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - A landscape of mountains and a body of water., Circa 1930-1950; ref905; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Mountains/Hills; Water; Landscapes; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - An aerial photo of the Citadel of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref906; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.6 x 8.3 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Aleppo, Syria; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Airplanes; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Citadel of Aleppo
  - An aerial photo of the Citadel of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref907; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Buildings; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Airplanes; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Citadel of Aleppo
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref908; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.9 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Landscapes; Airplanes
  - An aerial landscape., Circa 1930-1950; ref909; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 x 8 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Landscapes; Aleppo, Syria; Airplanes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of men conversing in a car., Circa 1930-1950; ref910; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 x 7.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Cars/Trucks; Men; Buildings; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref911; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.2 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Buildings; Aleppo, Syria; Airplanes; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - A group portrait of a man and a woman outdoors., Circa 1930-1950; ref912; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.2 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Men; Women; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a man (linked ref912)., Circa 1930-1950; ref913; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.6 x 8.6 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Men; Landscapes; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints
  - A portrait of a woman with two dogs on a leash in the snow., Circa 1930-1950; ref914; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.2 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Women; Snow; Cars/Trucks; Dogs; Individual Portraits; Animals; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - A portrait of a woman with a headscarf smoking., Circa 1930-1950; ref915; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.7 x 8.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Women; Smoking; Cigarettes; Head Covers/Veils; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a woman (linked ref915)., Circa 1930-1950; ref916; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.3 x 7.9 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Women; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A portrait of a woman on horseback., Circa 1930-1950; ref917; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.8 x 8.3 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Women; Animals; Horses; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - An aerial landscape of the Citadel of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref918; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.3 x 8 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Airplanes; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Citadel of Aleppo
  - An aerial landscape of the Citadel of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref919; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.2 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Airplanes; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Citadel of Aleppo
  - An interior of a room with a radio, map, and golf clubs., 1944-1945; ref920; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Golf; Radios; Maps; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - An aerial landscape of the Citadel of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref921; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Aleppo, Syria; Buildings; Airplanes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Citadel of Aleppo
  - An aerial landscape of the Citadel of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref922; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.3 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Photographic Prints; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Airplanes; Aleppo, Syria; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Citadel of Aleppo
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref923; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.8 x 7.9 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Buildings; Airplanes; Aleppo, Syria; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - An aerial landscape of a section of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref924; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.6 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Aleppo, Syria; Buildings; Airplanes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Landscapes
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref925; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.2 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Aleppo, Syria; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Airplanes
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref926; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.9 x 8.6 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - A portrait of a man standing next to the "Southern Star" airplane in a field., Circa 1930-1950; ref927; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.8 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Airplanes; Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria; English Writing
  - A portrait of a man smoking next to an airplane., Circa 1930-1950; ref928; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.6 x 8 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Men; Airplanes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Aleppo, Syria
  - An aerial landscape of the Citadel of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref929; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.6 x 8.7 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Aleppo, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Buildings; Airplanes; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Citadel of Aleppo
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref930; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.3 x 8 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Buildings; Airplanes; Aleppo, Syria
  - A group portrait of two people on horseback., Circa 1930-1950; ref931; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.7 x 8.7 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Men; Women; Horses; Animals; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - An aerial landscape of the Citadel of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref932; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.3 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Buildings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Airplanes; Landscapes; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Citadel of Aleppo
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref933; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.9 x 7.9 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Buildings; Aleppo, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Airplanes
  - An aerial landscape of a village., Circa 1930-1950; ref934; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Airplanes; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref935; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.8 x 8.2 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Buildings; Airplanes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Aleppo, Syria
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref936; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref937; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Airplanes; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Aleppo, Syria
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref938; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.8 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Aleppo, Syria; Buildings; Airplanes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes
  - An aerial landscape of a village., Circa 1930-1950; ref939; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Aleppo, Syria; Airplanes; Buildings
  - A picture of a man on horseback jumping a hurdle., Circa 1930-1950; ref940; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.4 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Men; Aleppo, Syria; Animals; Horses; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a woman wearing a hat., Circa 1930-1950; ref941; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.9 x 18 cm (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Women; Hats; Aleppo, Syria
  - A portrait of a woman wearing a hat., Circa 1930-1950; ref942; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.9 x 17.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Women; Hats; Clocks/Watches; Aleppo, Syria; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - A portrait of a woman wearing a hat., Circa 1930-1950; ref943; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.9 x 17.6 cm (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Hats; Jewelry; Women; Aleppo, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A portrait of a woman wearing a hat., Circa 1930-1950; ref944; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.6 x 17.6 cm (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Women; Hats; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a woman wearing a hat., Circa 1930-1950; ref945; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.9 x 17.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Women; Hats; Aleppo, Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a woman wearing a hat and eating., Circa 1930-1950; ref946; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.7 x 17.2 cm (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Women; Hats; Food; Jewelry; Aleppo, Syria; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - A portrait of a woman wearing a hat., Circa 1930-1950; ref947; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 31.2 x 20.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Studio Series II (Box 7)
  - A studio portrait of a woman wearing a scarf., Circa 1960-1975; ref948; Armous Studio, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 4.3 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Women; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Damascus, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man (linked ref 951, 952, 970, 971, 973, 974, 975, 976, 982, 983, 984, 986, 987)., 1972; ref949; Studio Damashk, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 6.3 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of a boy with his hand on his face., March 1966; ref950; Studio Echbelia, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6.2 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Boys; Children; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing glasses (linked ref 949, 952, 970, 971, 972, 973, 974, 975, 976, 982, 983, 984, 986, 987)., 28 October 1962; ref951; Studio Adib, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Damascus, Syria
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing glasses (linked ref 949, 951, 970, 971, 972, 973, 974, 975, 976, 982, 983, 984, 986, 987)., 28 October 1962; ref952; Studio Adib, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Damascus, Syria
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1960-1975; ref953; Studio Fardosse, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.6 x 4.2 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Boys; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Damascus, Syria; Children
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1960-1975; ref954; Studio Fardosse, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 4.2 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Boys; Children; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., 12 August 1960; ref955; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.2 x 6.2 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Men; Facial Hair; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., 13 October 1970; ref956; Studio Al Qusour, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Facial Hair; Men
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., Circa 1960-1975; ref957; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.4 x 3.4 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Men; Facial Hair; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a girl wearing a patterned dress., 26 March 1966; ref958; Studio Jacques, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.1 x 5.9 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Damascus, Syria; Girls; Children; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of a man., 9 October 1962; ref959; Studio Adib, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.4 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Damascus, Syria
  - A group portrait of a boy and a baby., Circa 1960-1980; ref960; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.8 x 7 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Boys; Children; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., 12 March 1964; ref961; Studio Star, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6.3 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Damascus, Syria; Facial Hair; Men; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing glasses with a mustache., 22 April 1982; ref962; Studio Star, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.9 x 7 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Men; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of two men., March 1962; ref963; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8 x 6.2 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Men; Facial Hair; Facial Hair; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man., Circa 1954; ref964; Photo Katchadour, Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Men; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a boy holding a candle and a book., Circa 1960-1980; ref965; Photo Mohammad, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.2 x 8.5 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Boys; Children; Aleppo, Syria; Religion; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A group portrait of two boys holding hands., 6 June 1974; ref966; Photo Liban, Beirut, Lebanon; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.7 x 8.9 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Beirut, Lebanon; Boys; Children; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A studio portrait of two women., Circa 1960-1980; ref967; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.4 x 8.5 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Syria; Women; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Arabic Writing
  - A group portrait of four children and a votive statue of Mary., Circa 1960-1980; ref968; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.9 x 8.7 cm (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Children; Religion; Toys; Churches; Boys; Girls; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a woman and a man., 1954; ref969; Photo Liore, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.3 x 8.5 cm (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Aleppo, Syria; Men; Women; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Armenian Writing; Facial Hair
  - A studio portrait of a man (linked ref 949, 971, 973, 974, 975, 976, 982, 983, 984, 986, 987)., Circa 1970-1975; ref970; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 7, Folder 3)